

# **CAREER VISION**

Seeking a challenging, responsible and dynamic position in renowned organization where all my energies, knowledge and experience can be effectively utilized for benefit of the organization and enhancement of my career.

## **CONTACTS**

- Abu Dhabi, UAE
- +971 501640780
- approvaltrick@gmail.com
- gejawad
- https://onfusion.github.io/

# **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Communication	
Team Work	
Creativity	
Dedication	
Confidence	
Leadership	_

# **Jawad Bhatti**

Sr. Consultant Salesforce / Front-End Developer

#### **PROFILE**

Creative Front-End Developer offering 9+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Over the past 9 years, as a Frontend Developer, I have designed, developed, and launched customized, highly responsive websites and e-commerce solutions using advanced technologies. In addition, I have consistently met client expectations and project milestones while working effectively in deadline-driven environments.

# **TECHNOLOGY & FRAMEWORK**

- SFCC, SFRA, Demandware
- Material UI, Semantic UI
- Vue JS

- **Twitter Bootstrap**
- Angular JS, Angular
- React JS, Knockout JS

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML/HTML5
- SASS/LESS, Compass
- Pug JS
- Node JS
- PHP, MySQL
- WordPress, Shopify
- Git, SVN, GitHub
- UI/UX Designin

- CSS/CSS3
- JavaScript, jQuery
- TypeScript
- C++
- Laravel
- Gulp, Grunt, Webpack
- NPM, Yarn, Composer
- Photoshop

# **WORK HISTORY**

#### Systems Ltd.

Lahore

2021 - Present

#### Sr. Consultant Salesforce

Sr. Front-End Developer

Provide Salesforce Commerce Cloud (SFCC) technology expertise for solution design and technical implementation. Design, code, unit test, and code review iterative improvements to platform.

Worked closely with programmers and clients to meet

project requirements, goals, and desired functionality.

Developed and integrated customized themes into WordPress, Drupal, and PHP based web applications.

# Zepto Systems PVT Ltd.

Islamabad

2015 - 2021

Faisalabad

2014 - 2015

Sitara InfoTech PVT Ltd. • Web Developer

Designed and maintained both corporate and client websites, using scripting languages and CMS including WordPress. Developed websites from front to backend using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, and PHP.

# **EDUCATION**

2021

#### Master's Degree

Virtual University of Pakistan

2009 - 2011

#### **Bachelor**

Punjab University of Lahore

2007 - 2009

#### **Intermediate**

P.B.T.E of Lahore, Pakistan

2006 - 2007

#### Matric

B.I.S.E Faisalabad, Pakistan

# **CERTIFICATION**

2015

# **Web Development**

EVS Learning Faisalabad, Pakistan.

2013

# Web Designing

ApTech, Pakistan

2011

**CCA** (Course of computer application)

TEVETA - P.B.T.E Lahore, Pakistan

# **LANGUAGE**

**English** 

Urdu

# Digital Solution PVT Ltd. Jr. Web Developer

Faisalabad 2013 - 2014

Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams to improve the website and applications, increasing conversion rates by 40%. Performed there for outsource projects based on WordPress CMS.

### IT Empire PVT Ltd.

Faisalabad 2011 - 2013

#### Jr. Web Developer

Performed in this organization as Jr. developer, operate several websites based on B2Evolution, WordPress and Joomla CMS.

#### **PROJECTS**

# <u>KaDeWe</u>

Salesforce (SFCC/SFRA), Node JS https://kadewe.de/

### **EBW**

Salesforce (SFCC/SFRA), Node JS https://everythingbutwater.com/

#### Movein 4

PHP Zend Framework, Knockout JS https://poilet.mymovein.com/

# **QS Hub**

Angular JS, Node JS, PHP https://qs-hub.qs.com/

#### **QS - Quacquarelli Symonds**

WordPress, JavaScript, PHP https://www.qs.com/

# **Top Universities**

Drupal, JavaScript, SCSS, PHP https://www.topuniversities.com/

#### Top MBA

Drupal, JavaScript, SCSS, PHP https://www.topmba.com/

#### **KTech Solutions Ltd.**

WordPress, JavaScript, PHP http://www.ktechsol.com/

# **HOBBIES / INTEREST**

?

Computing

?

Gaming

Photography

?

?

Travel

?

Music